<string_table>
    
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_dad">
		<text>Note in a lockbox</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_dad_descr">
		<text>Mischa,\n \n
			I won't be making it back home. Take this artifact and give it to Sakharov mentioning my name; he will arrange for the treatment to be given to mama. Finch's gang have me cornered - one way or another, I have to end this.\n \nI'm sorry, brother. Give my love to Zlata when you see her.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_tarkov">
		<text>Note in a secure case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_tarkov_descr">
		<text>Curse this place! Today Eagle stumbled into one of those damn anomalies when we were fighting off a pack of dogs, a piece of his thigh hit me square in the face! We couldn't find his dogtag, parts of him were scattered in a twenty yard radius at least. Jackal is starting to lose it too, I've been hearing him rambling in his sleep. I hope those TerraGroup bastards we're chasing down are rotting in some radioactive ditch somewhere, I signed up to shoot looters and capitalists, not deal with this bizarre shit. Let's hope I get the fuck out of here soon. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_bandit">
		<text>Note in a briefcase</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_bandit_descr">
		<text>Flea, if you're reading this, don't take the habar to Chief's men like we planned, he tried to fucking kill us! Only Vor and I made it out - he thinks because Borov gave him control of the Cemetary he's the big boss now and can backstab his brothers! Take this loot and go to Sultan, hire some hitters so we can teach that bitch his place. I'll meet you at the bridge. \n \n- Worm\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_sniper">
		<text>Note in a rifle case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_sniper_descr">
		<text>Voron,\n \nOnce you find this, post up in the water tower. The snitch is currently hiding in with Freedom; at 2200 we will flush the rat out and he'll try to sneak his way past the checkpoint. Take him out before he does and make sure you get the flash drive off his body; I don't care what happens to the rest of him.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_digger">
		<text>Note in a case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_digger_descr">
		<text>Yuri, I finally hit pay dirt! I got your tip about the cache in the Swamps, I grabbed what I could and managed to make it back to safety. There's still a shit ton of stuff there so I'm going to make a return trip - saw some of those bandits snooping around so I'm going to take the SVT. Here's your cut for now. Hope it brings you luck! \n \n Viktor\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_birthday">
		<text>Note in a rifle case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_birthday_descr">
		<text>Hey bro!\n \n The boys and I wanted to say thank you for pulling our ass out of the fire so many times. We heard your birthday was coming up, so we called in some favors and pulled some strings to get you this fancy new toy. I know you keep complaining that your old SVU is a piece of shit, inaccurate, this and that, so we got you a real sniper's weapon. Enjoy it bro! We'll be back in the Warehouses whenever you want to stop by for a drink.\n \n- Pasha\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_mikhail">
		<text>Note in a toolbox</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_mikhail_descr">
		<text>Konstantin,\n \n Take these tools and bring them to Mangun. We're running low on tools and there's only so much a man can do with duct tape and fishing line.\n \n - Mikhail\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_orders">
		<text>Note in a survival cache</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_orders_descr">
		<text>
			Patriot,\n \nYour orders are as follows:\n \nMeet with Shinobi at rendezvous point Beta Rho Niner Two Five.\nUse the supplies disguises to infiltrate Point of Interest Kappa Oscar. There is usually a warrant officer situated outside to control access; use the provided money to bribe your way past.\nGive one package to Shinobi. Take the other package and deliver it to the fuel tanks located at Position Charlie. Set the timer for 22 hours.\nOnce you are done, rendezvous with Shinobi and exfiltrate to rendezvous point Alpha 4 for debrief.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_vodka">
		<text>Note in a survival cache</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_vodka_descr">
		<text>
			\nVodka! You're feeling stronger!
			\nVodka! No more feeling bad!
			\nVodka! Your eyes are shiny!
			\nVodka! You are the real man!
			\nVodka! Wipes away your tears!
			\nVodka! Removes your fears!
			\nVodka! Everyone is gorgeous!
			\nYeah Vodka!\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_transmute">
		<text>Note in an artifact case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_transmute_descr">
		<text>Senior Researcher Pavel,\n \nWe experienced some limited success with the transmutation of the 'Hourglass' artifact. While the application of artifacts in the Fruit Punch anomaly reacted as expected, subsequent addition of the Flash artifact into the field caused an unexpected and drastic surge in energy. Intern Andreychuk was knocked on his back and one of the field computers suffered liquid damage, but thankfully little harm came to our personnel or equipment overall. However, regretfully, our suits and field equipment have been mired in some horrid stench that refuses to go away! We will be requisitioning new equipment and selling our old suits on the black market. I am storing one ingredient for transmutation here; until we fine-tune the recipe I do not want to risk another incident. \n \nStaff Researcher Nikolai \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_spooky">
		<text>Note in an artifact case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_spooky_descr">
		<text>Head Professor Sakharov,\n\Yesterday a stalker by the name of Windy visited the Mobile Lab and sold us this very strange artifact. He claims it is the 'essence of a poltergeist'. We are uncertain where the origin of this artifact is - when we pressed the seller for questions, he refused to speak. The composition resembles that of a chunk of quartz, yet is as amorphous as wet sand. Sample floats at rest and exhibits mild gravitational anomalies to small objects nearby, such as rocks. As we lack the proper equipment in our lab, we are sending you this sample for further analysis.\n \nStaff Researcher Nikolai \n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_spankbank">
		<text>Note in a briefcase</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_spankbank_descr">
		<text>Hey, when you're done with your 'business' please close the damn case and clean up after yourself! If I find the damn pages stuck together I'm going to shove a Fireball up your ass!\n \n 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_grenade">
		<text>Note in a munitions box</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_grenade_descr">
		<text>Andrey,\n \nI filched this box from Spooner's store. With the way he's always smoking on duty, it's inevitable that the munitions warehouse is going to become a fireworks show. Take these lemons to the tunnel in Cordon west of where Kuznetsov's posted: you'll meet some Loners there with a box of artifacts. Bring Lyontsov and Romanenko with you - they can be trusted. Once you're done transacting, leave the artifacts where you found this box.\n \nSgt. Kovalenko\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_deathlamp">
		<text>Note in a Monolith Cache</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_deathlamp_descr">
		<text>BROTHERS, I HAVE SEEN THE LIGHT AND IT BURNS THE SOUL, IT BURNS AND HURTS AND I CAN HEAR IT AND IT MUST BE SEALED AND WE ARE CURSED THERE IS NO LIGHT THERE IS NO HOPE THERE IS ONLY THE PAIN AND THE HURT AH OH GOD IT HURTS NO PUT IT AWAY GET IT OUT IT HELP I CANT HELP NO PLEASE HELP ME
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_tourist">
		<text>Note in a shotgun locker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_tourist_descr">
		<text>
			8 September 2018
			\n \nFuck man, I'm dead meat!
			\nThat idiot Marko just had to open his mouth around that bitch Hip in the village! Bragging about how he had the Bizon shotgun and could shoot the balls off a Boar from 100 meters away! Well she heard us and made us a good offer, but that dumb fuck had to mouth off and say that he would only deal with her if she'd sweeten the deal with a blowie! That night we were camping near the train tunnel entrace, that bitch found us with a squad of some really serious looking motherfuckers! She put her handgun on Marko's junk and shot him, took off his fuckin' eggs! She told me to go bring her that shotgun or else she'd shoot my balls off next! Well Artem decided to run away, and my Marko is now sleeping it off in camp while I'm God knows where making sure this shooter is still here. Fuck this shit, I'm getting out of here! I'm going to leave this shotgun where it is and hope she finds it before she finds me! I hope her damn client has this gun blow up in his face.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_mechanic">
		<text>Note in a toolbox</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_mechanic_descr">
		<text>
			\n \n Personal log of Andrei Petrenko
			\n \n Yesterday was my birthday. I have been living in the Zone for almost one year now, give or take the occasional hop to the outside world to fetch supplies. I am starting to enjoy it here - the outside world never afforded me much respect, but here I put in honest work and enjoy the respect of my fellow man. There is something strange about this place, it hates technology and violence. I have cleaned and maintained more guns here just in the last year than in ten years as a gunsmith.  
		</text>
	</string>
	

	<string id="st_lootbox_note_mechanic">
		<text>Note in a shotgun locker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_note_mechanic_descr">
		<text>
			d
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_sheet">
		<text>Loose Document</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_sheets">
		<text>Old Documents</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_notebook">
		<text>Notebook</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_folder">
		<text>Folder with Documents</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_usb">
		<text>Flash Drive</text>
	</string>

	
	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_sheet1_descr">
		<text>A loose, typed document from military intelligence. The information is encrypted, as is standard procedure for the Military, who transport these documents in the absence of wireless alternatives and decrypt them by hand or with a special device. As such it is not too useful for the layman, though it is rumored that certain organized groups have access to the codes the military uses. The SSU would probably love to get this back, but other groups might get a lot of use out of this.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_sheet2_descr">
		<text>An old, loose page from a lab notebook. Might be interesting to some parties, but not too useful without the rest of it. The handwriting is messy and smudged, and being kept in less than adequate conditions has not done any favors for its readability. Potentially interesting to scientific groups.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_sheet3_descr">
		<text>A loose document in pretty bad shape. Some diagram is on it, which seems like a complex laboratory device. Liquid stains have rendered most of the typed text indecipherable, but it still may be worth a pittance.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_sheet4_descr">
		<text>A loose transport invoice detailing what items in what quantity were shipped to what location. Looks new, but you don't know if that's because it was produced recently or happened to be stored in a nice dry environment. Unfortunately the items are only referred to by a code, although the prices next to these items are quite interesting.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_sheet5_descr">
		<text>Some form of typed communication between two coded parties. No identifying marks of either of the parties are present, aside from two ciphered callsigns. Mercenary groups tend to pass information in this manner via one-time pads and dead drops to ensure absolute secrecy and anonymity for all parties involved.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_notebook1_descr">
		<text>A field notebook with scientific observations and drawings recovered from an Ecologist team. Several pages are encoded. The information inside is likely to be of interest to certain parties. The Ecologists will want this back, but other groups would certainly be interested in this as well.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_notebook2_descr">
		<text>Thick bundle of old papers from some administrative building. Most of the information in here is rather rote, like pay stubs, mundane reports, and printouts. There is definitely some useful information or patterns that may be uncovered here, but it will take a lot of time and patience.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_notebook3_descr">
		<text>This notebook has some accounting information in it, but the entries are encoded for security reasons. This likely belongs to either the military or other independent groups operating in the area, which makes such a document quite dangerous in the wrong hands.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_notebook4_descr">
		<text>Old notebook recovered from one of the X-Labs or a site adjacent to it.  Scientific groups will pay dearly for this, as any information inside can shed light on the true nature of the activities going on before the Second Incident.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_folder_descr">
		<text>Thick folder with documents recovered from a laboratory. Contains a treasure trove of information on experiments, observations, results, and comments, as well as administrative documents like technical documentation, invoices, communiques and reports. Extremely valuable information for any party.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_lootbox_docs_usb_descr">
		<text>Flash drive found in a briefcase. Common way to store and transport large quantities of information in a compact manner, although a computer is required to access the data.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>